Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Laura Huxley Papers
  - Interviews
    - Recordings
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "L. interview with Ruth B. Hawkins March 4 1998", 1998 Mar 4; UCLA Tape No. 282 (Box 102, Folder 22)
      - Diane McCutchen, holograph label reads "Interview 'Community Focus' Airs 11pm 11-28-04, 2004 Nov 28; UCLA Tape No. 283 (Box 102, Folder 23)
      - Laura Huxley, KPFK, holograph label reads "Aware w/ Laura Huxley 6-13-01", 2001 Jun 13; UCLA Tape No. 284 (Box 102, Folder 24)
      - Laura Huxley with Elizabeth Crawford, Interview, unknown radio program, Our Ultimate Investment, no date; UCLA Tape No. 285 (Box 102, Folder 25)
      - Laura Huxley, Interview, Hispanic Spectrum, Hosted by Monica Brooks, holograph label reads "Power 106 Interview Laura Huxley 7-17-1991", 1991 Jul 17; UCLA Tape No. 286 (Box 102, Folder 26)
      - Laura Huxley, Interview, Free Forum, Hosted by Terrence McNally, KPFK, 1998 Aug 13; UCLA Tape No. 287 (Box 102, Folder 27)
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "Interview, Phoenix Bookstore 3/13/91", 1991 Mar 13; UCLA Tape No. 288 (Box 102, Folder 28)
      - Laura Huxley, Interview, Faustin Interviews [?], 1990 Jun 2; UCLA Tape No. 290 (Box 102, Folder 30)
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "Radio Interview Penn", 1991 Jun; UCLA Tape No. 291 (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - Label reads: 40. Laura, Celebrity Salon, Dr. Kroger, no date; UCLA Tape No. 345 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Label reads: 33. Interview 6/23/68. [Laura Huxley, interview, Elizabeth Grunette, tape one], 1968 Jun 23; UCLA Tape No. 348A (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Label reads: 14. Interview Laura Huxley 6/23/68 [interview, Elizabeth Grunette, tape two], 1968 Jun 23; UCLA Tape No. 348B (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Label reads: 16. Interview Laura / Eliz. [Elizabeth] Grunette '68 [copy 2], 1968; UCLA Tape No. 352 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - Label reads: 41 Interview with KPFK '68; Label on reel reads: L.H. interview with Quigley KPFK, 20 Nov 1968; UCLA Tape No. 384A; reel one of two; play back speed is very slow (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
  - Lectures and Speeches
    - Recordings
      - Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, 1970 Oct 6; UCLA Tape No. 349A (Box Unknown container 934 for instance of Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, Folder 12)
      - Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, 1970 Oct 6; UCLA Tape No. 349B; Continuation of 349A. (Box Unknown container 935 for instance of Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, Folder 12)
      - Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, 1970 Oct 6; UCLA Tape No. 349D; Continuation of 349C. (Box Unknown container 936 for instance of Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, Folder 12)
      - Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, 1970 Oct 6; UCLA Tape No. 349C; Continuation of 349B. (Box Unknown container 937 for instance of Label reads: 30. A) Omega Center [Kansas City], L+P [Laura and Piero], Oct 6 1970, Part One, Day One, B) Omega Center, L+P, Oct 6 1970, Part Two, Day One, Folder 12)
      - Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, 1970 Oct 7; UCLA Tape No. 349I; Continuation of 349H. (Box Unknown container 938 for instance of Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, Folder 13)
      - Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, 1970 Oct 7; UCLA Tape No. 349G; Continuation of 349F. (Box Unknown container 939 for instance of Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, Folder 13)
      - Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, 1970 Oct 7; UCLA Tape No. 349H; Continuation of 349G. (Box Unknown container 940 for instance of Label reads: 25. A) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part One, B) Omega Center, 7 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day Two, Part Two, Folder 13)
      - Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, 1970 Nov 3-5; UCLA Tape No. 350C; Continuation of 350C. (Box Unknown container 941 for instance of Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, Folder 14)
      - Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, 1970 Nov 3-5; UCLA Tape No. 350B; Continuation of 350B. (Box Unknown container 942 for instance of Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, Folder 14)
      - Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, 1970 Nov 3-5; UCLA Tape No. 350D; Continuation of 350D. (Box Unknown container 943 for instance of Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, Folder 14)
      - Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, 1970 Nov 3-5; UCLA Tape No. 350E; Continuation of 350E. (Box Unknown container 944 for instance of Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, Folder 14)
      - Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, 1970 Nov 3-5; UCLA Tape No. 350A (Box Unknown container 945 for instance of Label reads: 31. A) Cumbres, First Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Cumbres, First + Second Day, 3-5 Nov 1970, L+P, Folder 14)
      - Label reads: 32. Harvard, 14 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Morning Session, 1970 Nov 14; UCLA Tape No. 351A (Box Unknown container 946 for instance of Label reads: 32. Harvard, 14 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Morning Session, Folder 15)
      - Label reads: 32. Harvard, 14 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Morning Session, 1970 Nov 14; UCLA Tape No. 351B; Continuation of 351A. (Box Unknown container 947 for instance of Label reads: 32. Harvard, 14 Nov 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Morning Session, Folder 15)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353A (Box Unknown container 948 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353B; Continuation of #353A. (Box Unknown container 949 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353C; Continuation of #353B. (Box Unknown container 950 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353D; Continuation of #353C. (Box Unknown container 951 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353E; Continuation of #353D. (Box Unknown container 952 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., 1970 Oct 24; UCLA Tape No. 353F; Continuation of #353E. (Box Unknown container 953 for instance of Label reads: 27. Toronto, 24 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Part One: Death and Rebirth, Part Two: shouting, Model[?] etc., Folder 17)
      - Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., 1970 Oct 24-25; UCLA Tape No. 354A (Box Unknown container 954 for instance of Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., Folder 18)
      - Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., 1970 Oct 24-25; UCLA Tape No. 354B; Continuation of 354A. (Box Unknown container 955 for instance of Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., Folder 18)
      - Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., 1970 Oct 24-25; UCLA Tape No. 354C; Continuation of 354B. (Box Unknown container 956 for instance of Label reads: 26. LxP [Laura and Piero], Toronto Oct 24-25, Seminar Session One: Transformation of E., Folder 18)
      - Label reads: 38. Anderson; Laura, One, no date; UCLA Tape No. 343B; Continuation of 343A.
      - Label reads: " Side 1 Imagination - Big Sur - Sat Apr [illegible] 64 - O - 612 Laura Huxley Side 2 [illegible] Apr 5 '64 - 628 Gene Sarfan [?]", 1964; UCLA Tape No. 431; not digitized
      - Label reads: 38. Anderson; Laura, One, no date; UCLA Tape No. 343C; CD
      - Label reads: 39. OBS. PT, 5/23/63. [Laura at Observation Point], 1963 May 23; UCLA Tape No. 344
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385A; reel one of six
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385B; reel two of six
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385C; reel three of six
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367
      - Label reads: 38. Anderson; Laura, One, no date; UCLA Tape No. 343A; CD
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385D1; reel four of six
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385E; reel five of six
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385F; reel six of six
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390A; play back speed is very slow
      - Label reads: One Rob and Laura [?]L. P. & Rose Spring 68 L. Sergent Smith & Elliot Two Ginny session scientology Spring 66, 1966-1968; UCLA Tape No. 391A; play back speed is very slow
      - Label reads: Big Sur Hot Springs April 3, 1964, Sat Eve Laura Huxley Seminar on Imagination, 3 Apr 1964; UCLA Tape No. 402
      - Label reads: First Part to be Rewound Second Part of Tape sent for transcript of my speech; Side A: Empty, Side B: Laura Huxley, speaking at unidentified event, [on the topic of psychotherapy ?], no date; UCLA Tape No. 404
      - Label reads: 38. Anderson; Laura, One, no date; UCLA Tape No. 343D; Continuation of 343C.
      - Label reads: 19. A) Irvine, L.H. [Laura Huxley], One, ? [illegible], Mai 24-25-26, ? [illegible], B) Irvine, 2-3, Mai 25, 1969 May 24-26; UCLA Tape No. 369A
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367D; Continuation of 367C.
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367E; Continuation of 367D.
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367F; Continuation of 367E.
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367G; Continuation of 367F.
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370A; Continuation of 370A.
      - Label reads: 19. A) Irvine, L.H. [Laura Huxley], One, ? [illegible], Mai 24-25-26, ? [illegible], B) Irvine, 2-3, Mai 25, 1969 May 24-26; UCLA Tape No. 369B; Continuation of 369A.
      - Label reads: 19. A) Irvine, L.H. [Laura Huxley], One, ? [illegible], Mai 24-25-26, ? [illegible], B) Irvine, 2-3, Mai 25, 1969 May 24-26; UCLA Tape No. 369C; Continuation of 369B.
      - Label reads: 19. A) Irvine, L.H. [Laura Huxley], One, ? [illegible], Mai 24-25-26, ? [illegible], B) Irvine, 2-3, Mai 25, 1969 May 24-26; UCLA Tape No. 369D; Continuation of 369C.
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367C; Continuation of 367B.
      - Label reads: 18. Irvine - Mai 26 '69, UCLA Tape No. 369F; Continuation of 369E.
      - Label reads: 21. Reel #1, 7075-A [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 1 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366B; Continuation of 366A.
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370B; Continuation of 370B.
      - Label reads: 18. Irvine - Mai 26 '69, 1969 May 26; UCLA Tape No. 369E
      - Label reads: 28. Cleveland, 19 Oct 1970, Day Two B, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 19; UCLA Tape No. 355H; Continuation of 355G.
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355A
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355B; Continuation of 355A.
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355C; Continuation of 355B.
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355D; Continuation of 355C.
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355E; Continuation of 355D.
      - Label reads: 22. Reel #2, 7075-B [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 2 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366D; Continuation of 366C.
      - Label reads: 28. Cleveland, 19 Oct 1970, Day Two B, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 19; UCLA Tape No. 355G
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367B; Continuation of 367A.
      - Label reads: 21. Reel #1, 7075-A [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 1 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366A
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370E; Continuation of 370E.
      - Label reads: 22. Reel #2, 7075-B [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 2 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366C
      - Label reads: 23. Reel #3, 7075-C [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 3 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366E
      - Label reads: 23. Reel #3, 7075-C [Laura and Piero, Aureon Workshop Reel 3 of 3], 1970 Nov; UCLA Tape No. 366F; Continuation of 366E.
      - Label reads: 24. A) Oasis - One, Oct 3 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, B) Oasis - Two, Oct 4 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], speed 15/16, 1970 Oct 3-4; UCLA Tape No. 367A
      - Label reads: 29. A) Cleveland, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], Day One, B), Cleveland, Day Two, 17-18 Oct 1970, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Oct 17-18; UCLA Tape No. 355F; Continuation of 355E.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390F; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390E.
      - Label reads: 15. A) One, ? [illegible] Center, Nov 13 '69, B) Nov. 13 - Laura Talk with K. Faber [Carl Faber], 1969 Nov 13; UCLA Tape No. 372D
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370G
      - Label reads: One Rob and Laura [?]L. P. & Rose Spring 68 L. Sergent Smith & Elliot Two Ginny session scientology Spring 66, 1966-1968; UCLA Tape No. 391B; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 391A.
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370C; Continuation of 370C.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390G; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390F.
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370D; Continuation of 370D.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390E; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390D.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390D; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390C.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390C; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390B.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390B; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390A.
      - Label reads: 35-37 Laura Huxley, Robert Gerard, Eugene Sagan, 3 parts (6 reels), circa 1970?; UCLA Tape No. 385D2; Continuation of 385D1.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371A; Continuation of 371A.
      - Label reads: 20. A) Tecate, Sept 18 eve 19, L+P [Laura and Piero], B) Tecate, Sept 19 eve 20, L+P [Laura and Piero], 1970 Sep 18-20; UCLA Tape No. 370F; Continuation of 370F.
      - Label reads: 15. A) One, ? [illegible] Center, Nov 13 '69, B) Nov. 13 - Laura Talk with K. Faber [Carl Faber], 1969 Nov 13; UCLA Tape No. 372B; Continuation of 372A.
      - Label reads: 15. A) One, ? [illegible] Center, Nov 13 '69, B) Nov. 13 - Laura Talk with K. Faber [Carl Faber], 1969 Nov 13; UCLA Tape No. 372A; Continuation of 372A.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371G; Continuation of 371H.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371F; Continuation of 371F.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371E; Continuation of 371E.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371D; Continuation of 371D.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371C; Continuation of 371C.
      - Label reads: 34. A) Counciling Center Seminars, July 24, Oct 20 [?] [illegible], Oct 29, B) Women [?] of Co. Center, Lecture Nov 20 '69, 1969 Jul 24; 1969 Oct 20; 1969 Oct 29; 1969 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 371B; Continuation of 371B.
      - Label reads: L. June 2 1971 L.A. STAN, 2 Jun 1971; UCLA Tape No. 390H; play back speed is very slow. Continuation of 390G.
      - Label reads: 15. A) One, ? [illegible] Center, Nov 13 '69, B) Nov. 13 - Laura Talk with K. Faber [Carl Faber], 1969 Nov 13; UCLA Tape No. 372C; Continuation of 372C.
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (1 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (2 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 3 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (3 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 4 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (4 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 5 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (5 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 6 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Laura Huxley, seminar?, Love, Not Love (6 of 6), 1964 Oct 2, 3, 4; UCLA Tape No. 7 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Laura Huxley, Ram Dass and unidentified others, Our Ultimate Investment [?], 1978; UCLA Tape No. 223A (Box 99)
      - Ram Dass, Dying, AAHO Meeting, Santa Barbara, CA, 1974; UCLA Tape No. 224; Two cassette tapes (Box 99)
      - Laura Huxley, Ram Dass and unidentified others, Our Ultimate Investment [?] (continued from UCLA Tape no. 223 A), 1978; UCLA Tape No. 223B (Box 99)
      - Ram Dass, speaking to an audience, unknown event, no date; UCLA Tape No. 225; Three cassette tapes (Box 99)
      - Laura Huxley, Ram Dass and unidentified others, Our Ultimate Investment [?], 1978; UCLA Tape No. 223; Side A: Laura speaking with unidentified woman regarding the guardianship of a child, Side B: Laura Huxley speaking with Ram Dass. REBURN - BIG SCRATCH ON CD. (Box 99, Folder 18)